Hello?
[I haven't heard]
[from you all afternoon.]
I fell asleep.
I'm getting discharged tomorrow.
I know.
Come pick me up?
Okay.
Is it going to work?
Of course.
I cut
my own hair.
Don't worry,
I've got this.
Your hair's too long.
Doesn't it bother you?
Yeah, it's covering my eyes.
I think
you'd look good with long hair.
No.
It's too much hassle.
Stop blowing.
Here.
I'll sweep down
the cut hair later.
How is it?
Does it look good?
Your little cut hairs.
Why keeping them?
As a keepsake?
Let's go down and get some sun.
Sure.
Let me untie it.
Tomorrow I'll be out,
and you can be
with your boyfriend every day.
Happy?
There's a nicer
spot ahead.
You haven't been here before?
No.
It's really beautiful.
It's okay.
I'm alright.
I told you we should get out for a walk.
Lu Xixiao.
Let's
play hide and seek,
okay?
Hide and seek?
Why the sudden
urge?
Remember I once said
something to you?
What?
See the vast world,
take the open road,
joy each day,
peace every year.
Why bring that up now?
Silly.
Congrats on being discharged.
I'm going to hide now.
You have to close your eyes.
You're really so childish.
Just close your eyes.
Okay, okay.
Eyes closed.
I'll count to ten, okay?
Ten,
nine,
eight,
seven,
six, five, four,
three,
two,
here I come.
Lu Xixiao.
Here I come.
I lied to you.
I never loved you.
I was getting close
to you only to
get money from Guo Xiangling.
Going to Yicheng with you
was only to
escape everything.
And
what I said before,
that I didn't make a deal with your father.
That was a lie too.
What are you saying, Zhou Wan?
All lies.
Stop.
I knew you wouldn't go,
so I made sure
you did.
I used you
from the start.
Zhou Wan,
come out and talk.
Please. Zhou Wan.
Come out.
Zhou Wan.
You can hate me.
Just forget me.
What do you mean, Zhou Wan?
Come out.
We're done.
Zhou Wan.
Zhou Wan, please.
Just come out, alright?
Whatever you need to say,
say it out here, please.
Zhou Wan.
Zhou Wan, just come out, okay?
I'll listen whatever you
need to say.
Zhou Wan, just come out, okay?
Easy, easy.
Thanks.
Take it easy on that, okay?
Easy.
Well,
I understand you're in a bad mood.
You just recovered.
Can you drink less?
Relationships have fights,
it's normal.
Just make up later.
Wait a few days and you two
will calm down,
then reconcile.
That's what Gu Meng and I do.
Good evening, everyone.
I'm Lin Na.
I want to sing a song
for someone.
He happens to be here tonight.
And it's
Sunday night right now.
Are you okay?
So here's
Date on A Sunday Night
for
Lu Xixiao.
You know her?
She seems to be from Brightmoor.
♪Light a candle glow♪
♪on his face.♪
Why another one?
♪If voice is hoarse,♪
♪more fantasies arise.♪
♪Warm evening breeze♪
♪fills the hallway.♪
♪Soaked clothes,♪
♪flowing waves.♪
♪Don't think of tomorrow,♪
♪or the next second turns away.♪
Sounds pretty good.
♪All the long jokes♪
♪fill every gap.♪
♪I don't want to roam.♪
♪Whatever faith, who cares.♪
♪The world's got nothing to do with me.♪
It's late.
A few more drinks and we're done,
alright?
♪Let me treasure all this in my heart.♪
♪The record spins.♪
Easy, easy.
♪Just stay here with me.♪
What are you doing?
♪Nothing to do.♪
I get it that
you're feeling down.
But you just recovered.
♪On a Sunday night.♪
Lu Xixiao,
I know you don't know me,
but
I've liked you for a long time.
So,
would you like to go on a date with me?
Date. Date. Date.
No, thank you.
No.
Thanks.
Okay.
Just go.
Let go back home.
You're drunk.
Let's go.
Let's go back.
Can't handle that?
I think he's more interesting.
With Junior,
there's a cardboard box too.
Why bring it over?
It's addressed to you.
Your stuff,
you deal with it.
Junior.
What? Thirsty?
Let's go.
A package from Yicheng?
You traveled?
I went out
for a bit,
left some stuff at a B&B.
The owner insisted on mailing them,
but I'm going to toss them.
Study notes?
You want to study?
Your handwriting is so delicate,
like a girl's.
Don't touch what's
not yours.
Sorry.
Are you mad?
Go ahead.
I'll leave then.
I'll walk you out.
What do you want to say? Spill it.
Let's stop seeing each other.
Give me a reason.
I'm just tired.
You know?
You're not that great anyway.
[The number you have]
[dialed is busy,]
[please try again later.]
[The number you have dialed]
[is busy,]
[please try again later.]
[The...]
[The number]
[you have dialed...]
[you have dialed]
[is busy.]
[The number]
[you have dialed]
[is busy.]
[The number]
[you have dialed]
[is busy,]
[please try again later.]
[The number you have dialed]
[is busy,]
[please try again later.]
[The number]
[you have dialed]
[is busy,]
[please try again later.]
[The number you have dialed...]
Bless Wan
with good exam results next year.
[Bless her]
[with a smooth life,]
happiness,
and joy.
Bless Xixiao
with a life of happiness and peace.
Bless Xixiao with a life of happiness and peace.
Zhou Wan,
just say
you love me,
[and I'll forgive everything.]
Lu Xixiao,
I don't love you.
I've been lying to you all along.
Don't let me see you again,
or I'll make you
beg me crying.
[That was a long,]
[failed,]
[deceitful summer.]
No, look.
Only I and Jiang Yan got
the least.
So what?
Ten yuan? You had the nerve?
Hilarious.
You only offered ten yuan?
A hundred,
and I'll take
this wind power project.
Who wants this?
Is that all you got?
I, I'll take
this call.
One sec.
It's a girl, right?
Definitely.
Kills the fun.
Yeah.
Who wants it?
I do.
Twenty.
I'm offering a hundred.
I said a hundred.
Hello? Mom.
Yan,
when are you coming back?
Mom, what?
It's noisy here.
I didn't catch that.
When are you coming back for the holiday?
Mom,
I'm not planning to
come back for the holiday.
Should I buy you a train ticket?
Did you get one yet?
Mom,
just let me live on my own from now on.
Yeah.
Kills the fun.
Who wants it?
I do.
New Year again,
a year older.
So pretty.
Where is he?
What's he doing over there?
He's dancing with Zhou Wan.
That's too lonely.
I'll go keep him company.
Don't.
[I thought]
[reckless]
[defiance and escape]
[were unsharpened swords,]
[drawn bows,]
[able to match the whole world.]
[But our rebellion]
[turned out full of holes.]
[Maybe fate is always]
[unstoppable, inescapable.]
[At eighteen,]
[we can't save the world]
[or change]
[anyone.]
[If the price of changing this]
[is losing love and freedom,]
[then accept it,]
[lose,]
[and grow up.]
Morning, coach.
Morning.
Mr. Niu,
Zhou Wan said
the other company may not
be as big as Boxing,
but they've handled decent projects.
Can't take them lightly.
They have just done
some projects of rural towns.
Why so nervous?
Look at you, so clueless!
But she also said
the other company operates
with both e-commerce and branding
simultaneously,
which is very competitive.
Enough.
That's just a way
to cut costs.
What do you know?
Always making a fuss.
But Zhou Wan said...
Zhou Wan, Zhou Wan.
Always going on about her.
Is she the manager or am I?
I don't get it.
What's she put in your drink
that you follow her blindly?
Besides,
I've been
in this industry
longer than she's been alive.
The pitch meeting is about to start.
Where's Zhou Wan?
I'll call her right now.
Hurry.
Daring to be late for the pitch meeting.
That big-shot top student
has quite the attitude.
Why so nervous?
Buck up.
Hurry, keep looking.
I'm getting old,
can't keep up.
Nice shot.
Still can't reach her.
From today,
she is no longer
part of Boxing.
Junior Zhang is here.
Later,
the pitch
is yours.
Me?
- I really can't do it.
- That's it.
Mr. Niu.
- You can do it.
- Mr. Niu.
Hurry up.
Mr. Niu, you've got way more
experience than me.
I'll get you a promotion and a raise.
Shall we start?
Yes.
Wantuo Group's
West Coast Town project pitch,
begins now.
Wantuo Group.
We're Boxing Construction.
Young lady.
You played really well.
That last shot.
Even if they got to it,
they probably couldn't return it.
Thank you.
I've heard
you're the real master, Mr. Zhang.
My little tricks
can't fool you.
You know me?
Well,
how about we play a round together?
I did come to see you.
We can play anytime,
but if we miss today,
the West Coast Town project
of Wantuo Group
will all be for nothing.
I announce
that Wantuo Group's
West Coast Town project
goes to
Xingrong...
Where are your manners?
Mr. Zhang.
Dad?
Why are you here, Dad?
Zhou Wan.
Check this.
And you.
How did you do the background check?
After this,
get to my office.
If you don't want the job,
let me know.
I'll file the report.
I announce
West Coast Town project
goes to Boxing Construction.
What?
No way.
Why?
Isn't that awkward?
Did you do something,
Zhou Wan?
They lost a lawsuit and got hit with a dangerous
building rating before.
Why didn't you mention
something that important?
They weren't the main defendant.
The construction was fine.
The developer added illegal floors,
which dragged them in.
It's not a real stain.
Junior Zhang
would see it your way,
but Senior Zhang is different.
He's
near retirement
and values reputation.
They hid the case,
so he lost trust
in their integrity,
which could spell
trouble later.
You never disappoint,
Zhou Wan.
You should have told me!
I only got the materials this morning,
so I went straight to
Senior Zhang.
But with you here,
Mr. Niu,
no problem.
As your deputy,
I should clear the way
and top it off.
Let me help.
Well, over the years,
you've learned
a lot from me.
But the Everpeak Resort
project
is the top
priority.
I'm fair with rewards and punishments.
Work hard,
and everything
will be fine.
After you.
Thank you.
No problem.
I'm taking leave tomorrow.
Zhou Wan,
you've been perfect
attendance since you started.
Why take leave today?
I'm picking someone up at the airport.
What?
Who's so important you'd skip
the celebration?
Someone important.
I'm at the exit.
Are you off the shuttle?
You'll see me
as you come out.
I'm heading out
with my luggage.
To celebrate
the Wantuo win
and your return,
dinner's on me. Anywhere you like.
That's it?
Trying to brush me off?
What do you want then?
Aren't you exhausted from the flights?
A bit,
yeah.
But we've got
business to take care of first,
right?
I see you.
I see you too.
Welcome back.
Senior.
That's too formal.
Mr. Jiang.
Let's go.
What do you want for dinner?
My treat.
How about this?
Didn't see that
coming?
What are you doing?
I run around for you,
tend to your work and life,
and the first thing you do is hit me?
Put it away, now.
Eddie.
Hello.
Long time no see.
I'm changing agents.
Do you have a conscience?
- Get the suitcase.
- Lu Xixiao.
Thanks so much
for coming all the way from France.
Come on.
Don't mention it.
We've worked together so many times.
We're family now.
Well.
Guess I have to count on you for this exhibition.
Enough talk.
What's for dinner?
What?
Didn't you say you'd treat me to a feast?